Sorry.
すいません
Are you alone at this hour?
こんな時間にお一人です?
yes.
はい
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
I missed the last train.
終電逃しちゃって
Oh, are you serious?
あ、マジですか?
We're together.
一緒っすね
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
Your job?
お仕事?
Is it over?
終わりです?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうです
That's right.
そうなんですね
Isn't it dangerous to be alone?
一人危なくないですか?
I've been waiting for a while.
ちょっと待ってたんですよね
What should I do?
どうしようか
Oh, is it true?
あ、 本当 ですか?
Oh, oh, I see.
え、あ、そうか
I'm not a dangerous person at all.
僕、ちょっと全然危ない人じゃないんで
Well, that's totally true.
まあ、全然あれっすよ
It's a useless suggestion though.
ダメ元の提案ですけど
I'm staying at a hotel near this station.
僕、この駅の近くのホテルに泊まってるんですけど、
So I thought I'd just kill some time,
そこでちょっと、まあ、暇つぶしてと思って、
yes.
はい
Would you like to have a drink with me?
ちょっと一緒に飲んだりしません?
Oh, is that okay?
あ、いいんですか?
あ、いいですか?
vice versa.
逆に
Not at all, yes.
全然、はい
It's quite light though.
結構軽いですけど
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
yes.
はい
I've been waiting.
待ってたんです
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
yes.
はい
Well, work is tomorrow.
え、お仕事とかは明日
holiday?
休み?
Ah, I'm on vacation.
あ、休みです
Oh, what, are you serious?
あ、え、マジですか?
yes.
はい
Well then, shall we go?
え、 じゃあ、行きますか?
Oh, please.
あ、お願いします
Yes, that's it.
はい、やば
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Really.
本当に
That's suspicious, me.
怪しいっすよ、僕
Eh, it's okay.
え、大丈夫です
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Is it true? Then, yes.
本当か、じゃあ、はい
Well then, I won't do anything.
じゃあ、なんもしません
yes.
はい
So, do you want to sit here?
じゃあ、ここに座りますか?
Yes, yes.
うん、はい
Is that quite the case?
結構あれっすか?
Do you drink alcohol?
お酒飲むんすか?
normally.
普段
Ah, I'll drink.
あ、飲みます
Ah, that's nice.
あ、いいですね
A little lemon sour or something.
ちょっとレモンサワーとか結構
Yeah.
うん
Just around here.
ちょっとこの辺で
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Why?
せっかくなんで
Because there is one.
一応ありますので
I'll go with this.
僕はこれで行きます
Anyway, I'll do it right away.
とりあえず早速ですけど
Why?
せ っかくなんで
After toasting.
乾杯してから
a.
あ
various.
いろいろ
yes.
はい
Well, the point is, I'm not killing time.
まあ、要は暇つぶしてないですから
Where are you going?
どっちに行きますか?
Well then, here.
じゃあ、こっちで
Ah, yes.
あ、はい
Well, for now.
じゃあ、とりあえず
yes.
はい
You have to work today.
お仕事っすよね、今日
It was work, right?
お仕事だったんですよね
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうです
Ah, well, thank you for your hard work.
あ、じゃあお仕事お疲れ様です
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
yes.
はい
That's good.
いいっすね
By the way, I'm sorry, but I suddenly called out to you earlier.
ちなみにすいません、さっき急にお声掛けしちゃいましたけど
yes.
はい
So, I said I was done with work.
で、お仕事終わりって言ってました
What do you do for work?
お仕事何されてるんです?
I work as a sushi chef.
仕事は下寿司をやってます
Seriously?
マジっすか?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんです
It's a serious job.
真面目なお仕事っすもんね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうです
Sorry, I just thought it was kind of erotic.
す いません、なんかエロって思っちゃいました
It is said after all.
やっぱり言われます
That's what you say.
言われますよね
It's not a particularly erotic job.
別にエロい仕事じゃないですよね
It's not an erotic job.
エロい仕事じゃないですよね
It's serious work.
真面目な仕事です
It's serious work, isn't it?
真 面 目 な 仕 事 ですよね
If you think about it, I think so.
よく考えればそうだったと思って
that's right.
そうです
That's right.
そうですよね
Oh, and before that, work is the same,
あ、そう前にお仕事もそうだけど、
Is it okay if I ask your name?
お名前とか聞いても大丈夫です?
This is Minami.
みなみです
Oh, Minami-san.
あ、みなみさん
It feels like Minami from Shimo Sushi.
なんか下寿司のみなみって感じですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
This is Minami.
みなみです
That's nice.
いいですね
Minami-san happens to be like this quite a lot.
みなみさんは結構こういうことあるんですよ
I feel like I'm going to work late.
仕事遅くなってみたいな
Yes, there is.
ありますね
Do you often get late and miss the last train?
遅くなって終電を逃すことがよくあるかっていう
yes.
はい
Do you not often drink like this?
こうやって飲むことあんまないですか?
Isn't this the first time we've met?
初対面じゃないですか?
Do you feel like it happens sometimes?
たまにあるって感じですか?
yes.
はい
Oh, that was no good.
あ、ダメだったね
I think it's possible sometimes.
たまにありそうって思ってます
Do you think it might happen sometimes?
たまにありそうって思ってる?
That's what I'm thinking.
思ってることですね
Not after going out for drinks today,
今日は別に飲みに行った後とかじゃなくて、
Are you really done with work?
本当に仕事終わり?
I'm really done with work.
本当に仕事終わり
Oh, is that so?
あ、 そうなんですか?
I don't know if it's because I've heard of Shimo Sushi.
なんか下寿司って聞いたからか分かんないですけど、
It's coming out a little.
ちょっと出てますよね
What do you mean?
どういうことですかね?
No, something is coming out.
いや、なんか出てますよね
sex appeal?
色気?
Will you do it?
やります?
there is.
あります
I'm surprised now.
びっくりした、今
I hear you're going to do it.
やりますって聞こえてる
I was really surprised.
本当にびっくりしましたね
Yes, it happened suddenly.
はいって急になりましたよね
That's not true.
違いますね
Is alcohol strong?
お酒は強いんですか?
I haven't heard that it's that strong, but
そこまでが強いとは聞かないんですけど、
Depending on your position that day...
その日のポジションによっては...
There are times like that, and there are times when I can drink quite a lot.
そういう時もあれば、結構飲めるときもあるんですけど
Don't people around you move faster when you're tired?
疲れてると周り早くないですか?
It's early.
早いです
Are you tired today?
今日疲れてます?
I'm a little tired, so it might be early.
若干疲れてるんで、早いかもしれない
Well then, in moderation.
じゃあ、ほどほどに
Is it a little far from home today?
今日こっから家はちょっと遠目なんですか?
It's far away.
遠目です
Is it okay to work tomorrow?
明日は仕事とか大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you off tomorrow?
明日休みですか?
Now, wouldn't it be difficult if you had to work tomorrow too?
これでね、明日も仕事だったら大変じゃないですか?
Work...
仕事の...
Do you go out drinking even if you have to work?
仕事あってもお酒飲みに行ったりとかしますか?
I'll do it.
しちゃいます
is that so.
そうですか
It's tough, all right.
タフですね、結構
Surprisingly.
意外と
Isn't alcohol delicious?
美味しいじゃないですか、お酒
Isn't it the best after work?
仕事終わりの最高じゃないですか
Oh, you say?
ああ、と言うんですか?
Don't tell me.
内緒で
Is it a secret?
内緒なんですか?
Don't tell me.
内緒で
Is it a secret?
内緒なんですか?
She is more beautiful in the light than in the dark.
暗いところより明るいところが美人ですね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I thought it was dark magic.
暗闇マジックかと思ったんですけど
It happens often.
よくありますよね
I wonder if this happens often.
よくあるんですかなと思ったら
The brighter it was, the more beautiful it was.
明るい方が綺麗でしたね
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are all the people in your workplace full of women?
しかじゅうしゅうの方って、職場は女性ばっかりですか?
Yes, there are many women.
そうですね、女性が多いですね
That's why we had to meet each other.
だから、どうしても出会いっていうか
Maybe not.
ないかもしれないです
Or rather, a workplace full of women...
というかなんか、女性ばっかりの職場って、
There seem to be a lot of things going on.
いろいろありそうなんですね
We're all good friends at my place, everyone.
私のところは仲いいですよ、みんな
Isn't everyone there?
みんないません?
everyone.
みんな
In general, there are quite a few.
一般的には結構ありますね
I hear it a lot in general, that's for sure.
一 般的にはよく聞きますよ、確かに
As far as I'm concerned, I think we're probably still good friends.
聞くんですけど、私のところはまだ多分仲いいと思います
I often listen to that in sets, right?
そこまでセットで聞きますよね、よくね
I feel like we're okay.
うちは大丈夫みたいな感じ
surely.
確かに
It's also quite stressful and difficult.
結構ストレスとか、しかじゅうしゅうの方も大変ですよね
No, but it's difficult.
いや、でも大変です
I think there are quite a lot of stress,
結構いろんなストレスがあると思いますけど、
It's stressful, isn't it?
ストレスはまりますよね
I have to drink alcohol.
お酒でも飲まないと
I can't do it.
やってられないですね
やってられないです
I have to drink alcohol.
お酒でも飲まないと
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Didn't you hear from me earlier?
さっき、僕より声かけられませんでした?
Wasn't there?
いませんでした?
No, there wasn't.
いや、いなかったです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
yes.
はい
Did you miss the last train?
終電逃した手でした?
I was so happy that I missed the move.
逃した手、ホヤホヤでした
Ah, good.
あ、よかった
It's dangerous.
危ねえ
Isn't it quite fast paced?
結構ペース入れて早くないですか?
is that so?
そうですか?
Is it quick to put it in?
入れて早い?
Is it early?
早いですか?
Isn't that also true?
それもないですか?
Well, what do you think?
いや、どうなんですかね?
What do you think?
どう なんですかね?
like tired
疲れのような
Feeling.
感じ
Isn't it already karate?
もう 空手じゃないですか?
yes.
はい
They come quite a lot.
結構来てますね
Yes, it's coming.
はい、来てますね
It's coming.
来てますね
It's early.
早いですね
The more stressed out people are.
ストレス溜まっている人ほど
I don't know, but that's the image.
分かんないけど、そんなイメージですよね
Is that quite like that?
結構あれですか?
Is this what you wear when you go to work?
お仕事の時、こういう服なんですか?
No, it's not.
いや、違います
Is it different?
違うんですか?
Like a uniform?
制服みたいな?
that's right.
そうです
Somehow,
なんか、
Can I have you take a picture for once?
ちょっと 一回撮ってもらっていいですか?
Can I have your picture taken?
撮ってもらっていいですか?
Can I have you stand up for a moment?
なんか こう、 ちょっと立ってもらっていいですか?
Ah, that's nice.
あ、いいですね
May I?
いいですか?
Does this feel like commuting?
これで通勤してるって感じ?
that's right.
そうです
That's fine.
いいですよ
May I?
いいですか?
I stood up.
立たしちゃった
sorry.
すみません
It's really cute though.
なんかすごい可愛いですけど
Can I take a closer look?
近くで見ていいですか?
Yes, that's fine.
はい、いいですよ
May I?
いいですか?
yes.
はい
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
Please listen.
聞いてくださいよ
Her underwear is cute too.
下着も可愛いんですよ
absolute.
絶対
picture?
え?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Her underwear is cute too.
下着も可愛いんです
I guess so.
でしょうね
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
What can I say?
何言っていいですか?
what?
何ですか?
picture?
え?
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
That's right.
そうですよ
But you don't know if it's cute, do you?
それ、でも可愛いことか分かってないじゃないですか?
yes.
はい
I have to see it.
見ないと
Please take a look.
見してください
What you see is a lie.
見て るのは嘘ですよ
picture?
え?
That's a lie though.
嘘ですけど
Is that a lie?
嘘なんですか?
Is it true?
本当なんですか?
Is it cute?
可愛いんですか?
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですよ
So can you show it to me?
じゃあ見せてもらうことできるんですか?
That's fine.
いいですよ
Well then, excuse me.
じゃあ、すみません
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Excuse me for a moment.
ちょっと、すみません
What color?
色は?
The color is pink.
色はピンクです
Ah, isn't it cute?
あ、可愛いじゃないですか?
It's pink.
ピンクです
pink?
ピンク?
yes.
はい
What does it feel like?
どんな感じなんですか?
picture?
え?
Cute pink eyes yes.
ピンクの 可愛い目の はい
The bottom is yes.
下が はい
It's a T-back.
Tバックです
Oh no.
やば
Please stop again.
もう一回やめてください
It's a T-back.
Tバックです
Oh no.
やば
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's true.
本当ですよ
please show me.
見せてください
Alright, let's start with the color.
じゃあ、ちょっと じゃあ、最初色から
So let's start with color.
じゃあ、色から
yes.
はい
It's pink.
ピンクです
Oh no.
やば
Wait a minute, that's terrible.
ちょっと待って、やばい
I can't see it.
見れないですね
Can't see it?
見れないですか?
I can't look directly at it.
直視できないですね
Wait a minute.
ちょっと、やば
It's a little scary, isn't it?
ちょっと、やばいですね
It's been coming quite a while.
だいぶ来てますね
Is it alcohol?
お酒ですか?
yes.
はい
Alcohol.
お 酒
It's pink, and it's a T-back.
で、ピンク で、Tバック Tバックです
Is it a T-back?
Tバックなんですか?
yes.
はい
It's a T-back.
Tバックです
Can I see if it's a thong?
Tバックかどうかを見せてもらっていいですか?
I'll show you.
見せてあげます
Oh no.
やば
Please take a look.
見てくださいね
Oh, wow.
あ、やば
It's a T-back.
Tバックです
Wait a minute.
ちょっと、やば
That's terrible.
やばいですね
Were you working in a thong?
Tバック勤務だったんですか?
I was working in a thong.
Tバック勤務でした
Wow, it's amazing that she's only good at wearing thongs.
やば、Tバックしか上手ってなんかすごいですね
Ya ba.
や ば
Nice one to watch.
見ていいやつ
Please take a look.
見てください
Ya ba.
や ば
Please take a look.
見てください
Is it OK to watch?
見るのOK?
yes.
はい
I see.
そうか
A lot of different emotions are coming out.
いろんな感情がちょっと出てきてる
yes.
はい
Ah, it's cute.
あ、かわいいです
surely.
確かに
And the top too?
で、上も?
Is it on top too?
上もですか?
Yes, it's true.
うん、本当です
You can also show me the top.
上も見せてもらっていい
Is it?
ですか?
Well, this is actually...
え っと、ここがそもそも...
here.
ここ
Oh, is this it?
あ、これですか?
There's a notch in there.
なんか切れ込み入ってますね
It's in.
入 ってますね
a.
あ
It's in there, isn't it?
入ってますよね
Eh, there's a little cut here as well.
え、ちょっと切れ込みここにも入ってるし、
It's included here too.
ここにも入ってますよね
yes.
はい
Isn't that the case?
そういうことないですか?
Huh, something...
え、なんか...
It's like T.
Tみたいなの
Ah, certainly.
あ、確かに
Oh no, wait a minute.
やばい、ちょっと待って
Are deer girls erotic after all?
やっぱ鹿女子の人ってエロいんですか?
Well, what do you think?
えー、どうなんですかね?
It's erotic right now, after all.
今エロいですよ、だって
Oh, really?
え、本当ですか?
yes.
はい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
terrible.
やばい
But I couldn't see any underwear.
でも、下着見えなかったです
ah.
あー
Can you take a look?
見てくれますか?
Please show me a little.
ちょっと見せてください
Well then.
じゃーん
Oh no.
やば
That's it.
じゃーんって
Well, just a moment.
じゃーんって、ちょっと
It feels like oh.
おーって感じですね
Huh, do you really like pink?
え、結構ピンク好きなんですか?
I love pink.
ピンク大好きです
Oh no.
やば
Underwear pink.
下着ピンク
Both the top and bottom are pink.
上も下もピンクですよね
Well, if you've shown me this far, I'd like to ask.
え、ちょっとここまで見せてくれたんだったら聞きたいんです
But.
けど
What color is the bottom of this underwear?
この、 この下着の下って何色なんですか?
Is it under your underwear?
下着の下ですか?
I feel like it would be better for you to take a look and decide for yourself.
それはちょっと見て決めてもらったほうがいいかなっていう感じ
That's right.
ですね
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうっすね
So, do you like pink?
じゃあピンク好きなのピンクとかですか?
It might be pink.
ピンクかもしれない
Oh, it's definitely cute.
え、絶対可愛いですよね
So please decide, is it cute or not?
じゃあ決めてください、可愛いかどうか
Ah, I'll decide, I'll decide.
あ、決めます決めます
I have to decide a lot.
めっちゃ決めるんで
A little color.
ちょっと色
Please decide.
決めてくださいじゃん
picture?
え?
Did you see it?
見えました?
I couldn't see it.
見えませんでした
Did you not see it?
見 え な かったですか?
Oh, I couldn't see it.
あ、見えなかった
Really.
本当に
Ah, I saw it.
あ、見えましたね
Did you see it?
見えました?
Her face is cute.
顔可愛くて
Please look here.
こっち見てくださいよ
I can see it.
見えます
Oh no.
やば
pink.
ピンク
Slightly brownish pink?
やや茶色ピンク?
Slightly brownish pink.
やや茶色ピンク
That's right.
ですよね
I agree.
そうですね
sorry.
すみません
I know this is that color.
こっちはその色ってわかったんですけど
What about this?
こっちは?
Are you here?
こっちはんですか?
Are there different patterns on the left and right?
左右で違うパターンはないですか?
Maybe there is.
もしかしたらあるかもしれないです
Yes, right?
はい、ですよね
Then please take a look.
じゃあ見てください
yes.
はい
Please touch.
触ってください
picture?
え?
What is it?
なんですか?
Please don't touch it.
触らないでくださいよ
Yes, I understand.
はい、わかりました
sorry.
すみません
I'm sorry for touching you just now.
ちょっと今、勝手に触ってすみません
Well, let's touch it.
じゃあ、触ってみます
I'll touch it.
触りますよ
Hey.
ねえ
Oh no.
やば
Don't you see the colors?
色見るんじゃないんですか?
I'm looking at color now.
色を見てます、今
Are you looking at colors?
色見てるんですか?
yes.
はい
I'm looking at the colors.
色見てますよ
I'm looking at the colors right now.
今色見てますね
both?
両方?
both.
両方
It's a bit dangerous, isn't it?
ちょっとやばいですね
Minami-san.
みなみさん
Is it dangerous?
やばいですか?
yes.
はい
Isn't it a little bad when you drink alcohol?
お酒入るとちょっと良くないんじゃないですか、
everytime.
いつも
picture?
え?
Is it no good?
ダメですかね?
I'm not saying it's bad, but I think it's generally bad.
僕はダメじゃないですけど、一般的にはダメだと思います
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだ
Still here,
まだ、こっちの、
Ah, the color here?
あ、 ここの、色?
There is something like this too, isn't it?
こっちもなんかね、ありますよね、
Color.
色ね
Yes, there is.
ありますね
What color is this?
何色ですか、ここ
It's pink.
ピンクです
What, here, what, is the bottom of this pink too?
え、ここ、え、これの下もピンク?
It's pink.
ピンクです
Why do you call it pink?
なんでそんなこうピンクということにします?
It's pink.
ピンクです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
What?
何が?
picture?
え?
This bottom is pink.
この下がピンクです
What is this down?
この下って何ですか?
No, it's amazing, I thought it must be something because you insist on it.
いや、すごい、言い張るから何かなと思って
Oh, what's that? I couldn't hear it.
あ、え、何かいいですよね、聞こえなかった
Hmm, it's the color of your pussy.
うーん、おまんこの色ですよね
Please don't say it so clearly.
そんなはっきり言わないでください
In this color of pussy.
おまんこの色で
yes pink
はい、ピンク
is.
です
I'll check it then.
じゃあ 確認します
confirmation.
確認
yes.
はい
beside
横
To.
に
Did you see it?
見 ました?
I couldn't see it because it was a little far away.
ちょっと距離離れてて見えなかった
It was definitely a beautiful pink.
やっぱ確かに、きれいなピンクでした
Oh, there was more.
あ、あとまだあった
what?
何ですか?
What's inside this inside?
この内側の内側は?
Inside inside?
内側の内側ですか?
inside inside inside.
内側の内側
This is inside.
内側ですね、これ
Inside?
内側の?
inside.
の内側
Do you mean inside?
内側ってことですか?
Ah, yes, I felt good now.
あ、そう、今いい感じでした
Do you mean inside?
内側ってことですか?
It might feel like it's a little more.
もうちょいって感じかもしれない
Inside.
内側
It's inside.
内側です
One more time.
もう一回
It's inside.
内側です
内側ですね
something.
何か
what?
何ですか?
something
何 か
I feel like there's a little bit of noise, so I'm sorry.
ちょっと 音が出た気がして、すみません
Why don't you ask me again?
聞き直せんじゃないですか
聞 き 直 せ ん じゃない ですか
Ah, then there was no sound.
あ、それじゃ無音になっちゃった
She's amazingly fair-skinned, and her dick and pussy are pink, too.
すごいなんか色白いし、 チクビをまんこもピンクで、
That's amazing.
すごいですね
thank you.
ありがとう
Minami-san told me earlier that it was pink.
ピンクって言ったの、ミナミさん先教えてくれたの
I agree.
そうですね
yes.
はい
picture,
え、
a little bit.
ちょっと
Let's try this just once.
これ ちょっと一回ちょっと試しに
Is that what it looks like when you take it off?
脱ぐとあれなんですかね
Even though it's erotic.
せっかくエロいのに
That's it, but could you please take it off for a moment?
あれですけど、ちょっと脱いでもらっていいですか
I want to take a closer look.
もうちょっとよく見たいんで
Is it true?
本当ですか?
The underwear is cute too, but...
下着も可愛いですけど、 ちょっと こう、
I really like the inside too.
その内側もすごく好きで僕は
Do you like the inside?
内側好きなんですか?
yes.
はい
I like the inside.
内側好きなんですよ
内側好きなんですね
I like the inside.
内側好きなんですよ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Inside, I'm sorry, I'm sorry that I hit you a little.
内側、すみません、ちょっと当たっちゃってすみません
I was right.
当たってました
Sorry for hitting you.
当たっちゃってすみません
What, what did you win?
え、何当たってました?
What did you hit?
何当たってました?
It hit me hard.
ちんちん当たってました
I don't say it clearly.
はっきりすごい言いません
Hey.
ねえ
Sting my pink pussy all the time
ずっとピンクのマンコを刺して
...
picture?
え?
Wow, it's so beautiful.
すごい、 すごい綺麗ですけど
Where did you go?
どこ行っちゃったんですか?
I went somewhere.
どこか行きました
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's smooth.
すべすべですね
Mangei is smooth.
漫芸すべすべですね
Isn't this slimy?
こっちヌルヌルじゃないですか?
Miyami is so honest.
みやみさんすごい素直
I'm an honest person.
素直な方なんですけど
There's alcohol in it.
お酒入ってるんで
Are you honest?
素直な方?
It's you.
お前です
This reaction is faint.
こっちの反応がうかす
Are you honest?
素直な方?
picture?
え?
What happened?
どうしました?
sorry.
すみません
picture?
え?
Can you see it?
見えてます?
Where am I being touched?
自分がどこ触られてるか
Can you see it?
いやいや見えてる?
Can't you see much?
あんま見えてない?
Well, I can't see it.
あ ん ま 見 えてない
Do you know where I'm being touched right now?
今どこ触られてるか分かります?
I understand.
分かります
Where is it?
どこです?
I won't say it.
言いません
Why don't you say this?
ここ言わないですか?
I won't say it.
言いません
Well...
じゃあ...
It's the clitoris.
クリトリスですね
Yes.
ありだ
It's the clitoris, isn't it?
クリトリスですよね
It's the clitoris.
クリトリスですね
Isn't it bigger than before?
なんかさっきより大きくなってない?
Is that what it is?
そういうもんですか?
That's what it is.
そういうもんですね
Ah, I guess that's what it is.
あ、 そういうもんでしょうね
Can I pick this up?
これつまんでもいいですか?
It's boring though.
つまんですが
Is it okay to be boring?
つまんじゃダメですか?
I'm starting to have a hard time picking things up.
なんかつまめるようになっちゃってる
Do you ever touch your clitoris?
クリトリスを自分で触ったりすることあります?
there is.
あります
What time is it?
どういう時ですか?
When?
どういう時?
how?
どうやって?
How do you touch it?
どうやって触るんですか?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
how?
どうやって?
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいじゃないですか?
No, I don't think so.
いや、そんなことないと思います
I don't think it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしくないと思います
Aren't you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしくないですか?
yes.
はい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいんですか?
yes.
はい
Oh, this is really embarrassing.
あ、本当に恥ずかしいですね、これ
already.
もう
No, that's a lie.
いや、嘘ですよ
It's not embarrassing.
恥ずかしくないですよ
Do you spread it out and touch it like this?
こうやって、広げて触るんですか?
yes.
はい
Touch, touch.
触って触って
Is it okay to have your clitoris licked?
クリトリス舐められるのはいいですか?
What do you do?
どうしますか?
I don't like it.
嫌
What do you do?
どうしますか?
It's nothing.
なんでもないです
It's amazing, I'm standing up.
すごい 立ってきてます、なんか
I don't like it.
嫌
Are you not standing?
立ってません?
I'm standing.
立ってます
What?
何が?
That's no good.
ダメですよ
Isn't it okay because I said it earlier?
さっき言ったからいいじゃないですか?
That's no good.
ダメですよ
Please tell me.
言ってください
I hid.
隠れちゃった
Is it okay to lick the clitoris, but is it okay to put your finger here?
クリトリス舐めるのはいくて、 ここに指入れたりするのは?
It's okay.
いいんですよ
Okay, what about today?
いいんですか、今日は?
Can't you enter it yourself?
自分では入れないんですか?
I'll put it in.
入れますよ
Are you going to put it in?
入れるんですか?
I can usually put it in.
入 れるんですね、いつもは
yes.
はい
Alone.
一人で
yes.
はい
I'm here today.
今日、僕いるんで
yes.
はい
I'll let you in, then.
僕入れますよ、じゃあ
I went in.
入っちゃった
入 っちゃ いました ね
Is that what happens when you insert your finger yourself?
自分で指入れるときもあれなんですか?
Can you tell if your pussy is closed?
マンコ閉まったなとか分かるんですか?
Somehow.
なんとなくは
Somehow, I guess.
なんとなくですかね
It's tightly closed though.
がっつり閉まってますけど
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It's tough.
きついですね
Is it tight?
きついですか?
Deer species don't really take their pulses.
鹿獣種の方って別に脈とかは取らないですもんね
I won't take it.
取らないです
取らないですよね
She's a nurse, after all.
看護師さんですもんね、それは
You can feel the pulse here.
ここで脈取れますね
Can you take it?
取れますか?
You can take it.
取れますよ
I feel like I'm getting great results.
めっちゃ結果が取ってる感じしますね
a little bit.
ちょっと
What is it?
なんですか?
It's making a lot of noise.
すごい鳴ってますね
It's twitching.
ピクピクしてますね
What is it?
なんですか?
Wasn't it twitching?
ピクピクしてませんでした?
I haven't.
してないです
Didn't you look at it objectively?
客観的に見てしてませんでした?
I haven't.
してないです
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I'm twitching when it feels good though.
気持ちいいとピクピクしてますけどね
Minami-san, are you the type who doesn't do much?
美奈美さんはあんましないタイプですか?
No.
ないです
I want to be twitchy though.
ピクピクになりたいですけど
yes.
はい
Is it like usual?
いつものようにですか?
As always.
いつものように
Isn't it always something like that, with men?
いつも何かあれじゃないですか、男性と
Why not?
や らないですか?
I'll do it.
やります
I always want you to do the same.
いつも僕もやってもらいたいですけど
Can't you look at deer girls with erotic eyes?
鹿女子の方ってエロい目で見られません?
When I told her I was a deer girl.
鹿女子ですって言うと
Erotic.
エロい
People say it looks erotic.
エロそうって言われます
Would you say it's erotic?
エロいですって言いますか?
I won't say it.
言わないですよ
That's what I'm saying.
言ってるようなもんですよ
I won't say it.
言わないですよ
Why don't you say it?
言 わないですか?
You don't say it, but you show it with your actions?
言わないけど行動で示すって感じですか?
Is it really okay?
どうしてもいいですか?
No, yes.
いや、はい
So is it okay if I do?
じゃあどうしてもいいですか?
please.
ぜひ
Your face is too big.
顔いすぎますね
Your face is a little too big.
ちょっと顔いすぎますね
No, because it's erotic.
いや、だってエロいですよね
It was so erotic that it made my dick angry.
エロいからチンコ怒らさったんですよね
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
Isn't that so?
そうじゃないですか
Even though we had just met.
さ っき会ったばっかりだったのに
Do you want to suck your first dick?
最初のチンチンしゃぶっちゃいますか?
I'm going to suck it.
しゃぶっちゃいます
Can I sit down for a moment?
ちょっと座っていいですか?
It's okay.
いいんですよ
It's a little scary.
ちょっとやばい
My waist.
腰が
I can't stand up.
腰が立たない
Waist.
腰
Mijimi-chan has a small mouth, but
みじみちゃん、口ちっちゃいですけど、
Will all of this be included?
これ全部入ったりします?
I'll give it a try.
ちょっとやってみます
copper?
どう?
tight.
きつい
Because it's big.
大きいから
Because Hin-chan is big.
ひんちゃん大きいから
Well then, now
じゃあ、さっ
tree.
き
amazing.
すごい
It's big.
大 きいです
I made it bigger so I would like to include it.
大きくしたんで、入れて欲しいです
Where?
どこに?
I want it inside my pussy.
まんこの中に入れて欲しいです
Do you want me to include it?
入れて欲しいんですか?
I would like you to include it.
入れて欲しいです
What is it for?
何用ですか?
I want you to put it in.
チンチン入れて欲しいです
Which one would you like to put where?
どれをどこに入れて欲しいですか?
Let me point it.
指 させて
I want your cock inside my pussy.
チンチンを、まんこの中に入れて欲しい
is.
です
Is it here?
ここ ですか?
yes.
はい
I made it stand by myself.
自分で立たせましたもんね
What's going on now?
今どうなってますか?
I understand and twitch.
わかってピクピクしちゃう
That's right.
ですよね
This makes me twitch.
ピクピクしちゃいますよ、これ
Why did you invite Egoi?
なんでエゴイ誘い方したの?
This is a bit harsh, isn't it?
ちょっとこれ、きついですね
It's tough.
き つ いですね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Well, it's very fitting, but
ね、しっくりめっちゃピンピンですけど、
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
It feels really good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいいです
Do you like men's penises?
男性のおチンチン好きなんですか?
I can enter it.
入れられるの
I love it.
大好きです
I was scared.
怖かったんだ
Just sit up.
ちょっと起き上がって
Shall I take off my top?
上脱ぎましょうか
Your boobs are really beautiful.
め っちゃおっぱいきれいですね
I haven't been out for a while.
ちょっと出てないですよ
It's out.
出てますよ
Shall I attach the skirt as well?
スカートも貼りましょうか
It's beautiful.
きれいですね
It's beautiful, isn't it?
きれいですね、やばい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
It feels good.
気 持ちいいですよ
It's a mess.
めちゃくちゃな
Oh, sorry.
あ、すいません
There might be some space.
ちょっと場所があるかもしれない
This might be better.
こっちのほうがいいのかもしれない
Is it in the middle?
真ん中ですか?
The middle one is better.
真ん中のほうがいい
真ん中のほうがいいですね
Oh, there's no hero.
あ、へろはない
It's so soft, it's amazing.
すごい柔らかいですね、やばい
I'm starting to get nervous again.
またギンギンになってきちゃった
Beautiful body.
体きれい
Really.
本当に
While rubbing your butt a little.
ちょっとお尻を揉めながら
body
体
It's beautiful.
き れいですね
TRUE
本当
To.
に
It feels like it's going to be my shoulder right away.
なんか、 すぐ肩になるんですね
We're already together.
もう一緒っすね
I'm getting older.
な っちゃいます
Can I say that?
いっていい?
Nakata-san, this isn't your first time eating this.
中田さん、食べるのは初めてでないでしょう、
perhaps.
多分
It's my first time.
初めてですよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I think it's a lie.
なんか嘘だと思う
A cute child.
可愛い子が